

COMPUTER ENGINEER

Antwerp, Belgium

🖸 haliliceylan | 😽 haliliceylan | 🛅 haliliceylan | 🔟 haliliceylan | 🐧 CENG390709073 | 📦 haliliceylan

"I am a dynamic and driven engineer who thrives on challenges and is dedicated to pushing the boundaries of what is possible."

Summary.

As a highly skilled and experienced engineer, I am passionate about coding and problem-solving. I have worked on a variety of projects in different languages and fields such as gaming, cybersecurity, operating systems, and Raspberry Pi. I am currently interning at a laboratory in Antwerp, where I am working on mutation testing of Simulink models. With my advanced technical skills and ability to quickly adapt and learn new technologies, I am confident in my ability to deliver top-quality results and guide my team members in complex projects.

Antwerp, Belgium

May 2021 - Sept 2021

Nov 2022 - Present

Work Experience _

University Of Antwerp, AnSyMo, LoRe Labs

STUDENT ENGINEER

Conducting mutation testing on Simulink models using Python.

- Developing a **Simulink plugin** for automatic mutation testing.
- Collaborating with team members and researchers on experimental projects.
- · Participating in workshops and seminars on software engineering and testing.
- Conducting research on new methods and technologies in the field of mutation testing.

Neta Solutions Mugla, Turkey Jan 2022 - Nov 2022

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

- Participated in **pentesting** and security audits of smart contracts.
- Developed smart contracts using Yul, Solidity, and Security Test. • Implemented **Proxy Contracts** to manage multiple ERC-20 and ERC-721 tokens.
- Created NFT (Non-Fungible Tokens) for gaming applications.
- Improved random number generation for fair and secure gaming.
- Collaborated with team members on design and implementation of blockchain solutions.
- Conducted research on new technologies and trends in the blockchain industry.

Neta Solutions Mugla, Turkey Sept 2021 - Jan 2022

BSC NODE OPERATOR

- Operate and maintain **Binance Smart Chain (BSC)** node equipment and associated network infrastructure.
- Monitor and troubleshoot network performance issues and take appropriate corrective actions.
- Perform daily checks and preventative maintenance on BSC node equipment and network infrastructure.
- · Coordinate with other teams and vendors for maintenance and upgrade activities.
- Ensure compliance with industry standards and regulations.
- Check and upgrade version of GETH (Go Ethereum) as needed.
- Write and develop special debug tracers in GETH and modify GETH as needed.

Google Summer of Code Internship (Cloud Native Computing Platform)

STUDENT DEVELOPER

• Contributed to the open source project "Buildpacks" within the Cloud Native Computing Foundation.

- Developed and completed acceptance tests for the project using GoLang.
- Made various **bug fixes** and improvements to the project.
- Participated in weekly meetings and contributed to decision-making within the project.

Neta Solutions Mugla, Turkey SR. FULL STACK DEVELOPER March 2020 - Sept 2021

• Developed a restaurant order management system using **AWS SAM** and **Terraform** in **Python**.

- Created a Laravel application and deployed it on AWS EC2, using AWS Codepipeline and Gitlab CI/CD for staging and automatic deployment.
- Developed Flutter and Laravel applications, using the Provider design pattern in the Flutter project and generating a Laravel REST API for front and mobile clients.
- Created an OCPI (Open Charge Point Interface) microservice application using Python, with RabbitMQ for microservice communication.
- Designed a **Gitlab CI/CD** pipeline for deployment of a **NuxtJS** project.

Neta Solutions Mugla, Turkey

FREELANCE REMOTE SR. FULL STACK DEVELOPER July 2019 - March 2020 • Developed and refactored a Laravel marketplace app.

• Created a **Flutter mobile app** for the marketplace.

• Actively used AWS, Docker, Linux, Bash, and Plesk for app deployment.

Neta Solutions Mugla, Turkey Apr. 2019 - July 2019

FREELANCE REMOTE JR. FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- · Developed Laravel and NuxtJS projects.
- Created a customized e-commerce application using Laravel.

HALIL İBRAHIM CEYLAN · RESUME **DECEMBER 6, 2022**

DiyezMedia

JR. BACKEND DEVELOPER

JR. BACKEND DEVELOPER

• Implemented a queue system for a Laravel e-commerce project.

• Developed a CMS application using ASP.net.

Gaziantep, Turkey Oct. 2018 - Nov. 2018

Gaziantep, Turkey Oct. 2017, Jan. 2018

Honors & Awards

DOMESTIC

2020	1rd Place, Developer Students Club Turkey DSC-FEST	Turkey
2019	Finalist, Siber Yıldız Capture the Flag	Turkey
2019	3rd Place , Hasan Kalyoncu University Global Game Jam19	Gaziantep, Turkey
2018	Finalist, Hasan Kalyoncu University Gastrobilisim Hackathon	Gaziantep, Turkey
2018	Finalist , Hasan Kalyoncu University Global Game Jam 18	Gaziantep, Turkey
2018	1rd Place , Hasan Kalyoncu University Unity Hackathon	Gaziantep, Turkey
2018	Finalist, ITU CEKIRDEK Big Bang Start-up Challenge	İstanbul, Turkey
2017	Finalist, Hasan Kalyoncu University Smart Life Hackathon	Gaziantep, Turkey

Presentations

Developer Students Club Turkey's DSCFEST event

PRESENTER FOR "DSC MSKU: CARBON FOOTPRINT PROJECT"

Turkev Sep 2020

- Presented on the Carbon Footprint Project.
- Discussed the psychological effects of **mobile applications** on reducing carbon emissions.
- Outlined the **tech stack** used in the Carbon Footprint Project.
- Provided a live demonstration of the project.

DSC MSKU and IEEE CS MSKU's Digital Weeks event

PRESENTER FOR "FLUTTER ON DARTPAD"

Turkey

Apr 2020

- · Developed a visual memory game with participants.
- Introduced the concepts of **Dart functions** and **variables**.
- Explained the use of **Flutter widgets** and state management.

Program Committees

2020	Lead , Developer Student Club Mugla Sitki Kocman University	Mugla, Turkey
2019	Tech Lead , Developer Student Club Mugla Sitki Kocman University	Mugla, Turkey
2018	Lead, IEEE Hasan Kalyoncu University Computer Society	Gaziantep, Turkey

Education

MSKU(Mugla Sitki Kocman University)

Mugla, Turkey Sep. 2019 - June 2022

B.S. IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

• Started as a student in 2nd grade

- Graduated with a 3.5 GPA and received the award for Outstanding Student • Thesis topic: "Mutation Testing on C++ Code generated based on Simulink models"
- · Invited to Antwerp University for further research on the topic of my thesis under the supervision of Prof.Dr.Serge Demeyer and Onur Kılınc-

HKU(Hasan Kalyoncu University)

Gaziantep, Turkey

B.S. IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING Aug. 2017 - Sep. 2019

DECEMBER 6, 2022 HALIL İBRAHIM CEYLAN · RESUME